live in a van what are your utility
bills zero how much is your rent
hopefully nothing what do you need
nothing they've been lying to you your
whole life you can legally live in a
Walmart Lowe parking lot for a few weeks
you can stay there and stack
money now for the the 20s something year
olds who can't afford housing in this
[__] up Market this is a very viable
solution and after a year of doing it
how much money will you stack up not
paying any rent any power any
water you see that little box right
there that's mobile internet what else
do you need dog hey you you winning
y'all are trade workers how much can
y'all make an hour here where do you top
out
at here you're probably going to top out
maybe $25 $30 an hour but how about
Jackson Hole Wyoming might top out at
$150 an hour why cuz it's a bougie ass
Town located in the national park and
there's no housing there the average
home sales price is about a million
bucks there ain't no construction
workers buying these houses they don't
have anybody to work there and you can't
go cuz there's nobody nowhere to stay
you have this van and you can go stay in
Grand Teton National Park and stack
money making 150 bucks an hour probably
working
612s hello Ain now you have $115,000 in
the bank and Winner's coming oh Viva La
Mexico I'm going to go down there and
drink margaritas and [__] Senoritas
y'all came to the right Ved day
gentlemen had doesn't have a shower in
it appreciate you
bro